const quiz3data = [
    {
      id: 1,
      question: "I remember being taken to the aquarium when I was a kid.",
      answersList: [
        {answer: "Passive voice", isCorrect: true},
        {answer: "Active voice", isCorrect: false},
      ],
      help: "Passive voice is the correct answer. Active voice: 'I remember somebody taking me to the aquarium'."
    },
    {
      id: 2,
      question: "I ___ to stay in the office until the CEO arrives.",
      answersList: [
        {answer: "tell", isCorrect: false},
        {answer: "was told", isCorrect: true},
      ],
      help: "We can use 'it + passive verb + that-clause' to report what is said by people in general or by an unspecified group of people. We can only use 'tell' in this pattern when it means 'order'."
    },
    {
      id: 3,
      question: "After the earthquake, governments and organizations around the world ___ aid to the people of Haiti.",
      answersList: [
        {answer: "sent", isCorrect: true},
        {answer: "was sent", isCorrect: false},
      ],
      help: "Active voice is the correct answer. Passive voice is: 'After the earthquake, aid was sent to the people of Haiti'."
    },
    {
      id: 4,
      question: "He managed to stole my bicycle without being seen.",
      answersList: [
        {answer: "Passive voice", isCorrect: true},
        {answer: "Active voice", isCorrect: false},
      ],
      help: "Passive voice is the correct answer. Active voice: 'He managed to stole my bicycle without anybody seeing him'."
    },
    {
      id: 5,
      question: "It ___ to build a new school next to the river.",
      answersList: [
        {answer: "has been decided", isCorrect: true},
        {answer: "decided", isCorrect: false},
      ],
      help: "We can use 'it + passive verb + that-clause' to report what is said by people in general or by an unspecified group of people."
    },
    {
      id: 6,
      question: "Everyone ___ to stay indoors during the hurricane.",
      answersList: [
        {answer: "was asked", isCorrect: true},
        {answer: "asked", isCorrect: false},
      ],
      help: "We often use the passive voice to report what people say, think, etc., particularly if we want to avoid mentioning who said or thought what we are reporting."
    },
    {
      id: 7,
      question: "He would like to be hired by Tesla.",
      answersList: [
        {answer: "Passive voice", isCorrect: true},
        {answer: "Active voice", isCorrect: false},
      ],
      help: "We can also make the passive voice using a passive infinitive in the same place as a normal infinitive."
    },
    {
      id: 8,
      question: "Andrew's friends started to respect his singing skills.",
      answersList: [
        {answer: "Passive voice", isCorrect: false},
        {answer: "Active voice", isCorrect: true},
      ],
      help: "Active voice is the correct answer. Passive voice is: 'Andrews`s singing skills started to be respected'."
    },
    {
      id: 9,
      question: "It has been announced that the new government will reduce the taxes.",
      answersList: [
        {answer: "Passive voice", isCorrect: true},
        {answer: "Active voice", isCorrect: false},
      ],
      help: "We can use 'it + passive verb + that-clause' to report what is said by people in general or by an unspecified group of people."
    },
    {
      id: 10,
      question: "She knew that her grandfather ___ this house in 1970.",
      answersList: [
        {answer: "had been built", isCorrect: false},
        {answer: "had built", isCorrect: true},
      ],
      help: "Active voice is the correct answer. Passive voice  is: 'She knew that this house had been built in 1970'."
    },
    {
      id: 11,
      question: "Dogs love being carried everywhere.",
      answersList: [
        {answer: "Active voice", isCorrect: false},
        {answer: "Passive voice", isCorrect: true},
      ],
      help: "We can also make the passive voice using a passive gerund in the same place as a normal gerund."
    },
    {
      id: 12,
      question: "It ___ to postpone the concert.",
      answersList: [
        {answer: "was agreed", isCorrect: true},
        {answer: "agreed", isCorrect: false},
      ],
      help: "We can use 'it + passive verb + that-clause' to report what is said by people in general or by an unspecified group of people."
    },
]

export default quiz3data